facewaretech.com 2018-11-01

# Privacy Policy | Faceware Tech

Last updated June 20, 2018

Faceware is committed to protecting your privacy. This policy explains how information is collected, what is done with that information, and what controls you have.  By using our website, you consent to the terms of this privacy policy.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.  When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, company/organization, or phone number.  At any time you may visit our site anonymously.

You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit to Faceware Technologies.  Faceware Technologies takes precautions  — including administrative, technical, and physical measures  —  to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse.  Faceware Technologies handles personal information both as a Processor and Controller, as defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679.  We do not share personally identifiable information with outside parties.  You may request to download the information you have shared through our services and have it updated or removed at any time.

Faceware Technologies also collects non-personal information  — data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual.  We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose.  The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it: We may collect information such as language, zip code, unique device identifier, location, and the time zone where a Faceware visitor uses our products so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our website and services.  We also may collect information regarding visitors’ activities on our website and from our other services.  This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our visitors and to understand which parts of our website and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

### To improve our website

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

### To improve customer service

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

### To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to keep you posted on Faceware’s latest announcements, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, our newsletters have detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom or you may ask us to stop at any time.

## How do we protect your information?

Information sent to us via the website is seen only by Faceware Technologies staff.  At all times, your information is stored in a secure management system that is not accessible by anyone other than Faceware Technologies staff.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.  This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We, therefore, will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to this policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using our online contact form or by using the information below.

**Faceware Technologies, Inc.**  
**4515 Van Nuys Blvd. Suite 301**  
**Sherman Oaks, CA 91403**
